<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>australia on comsemassim</title>
    <link>/tags/australia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in australia on comsemassim</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/australia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>mount martha and frankston</title>
      <link>/post/mount-martha-and-frankston/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/mount-martha-and-frankston/</guid>
      <description>First posted 4 years ago
The Brazilian guys and I took a Sunday to go to this beach on Mount Martha around 60km away from the city. It took us a tad more than 2 hours to get there. It was easy enough, just have to get the Frankston train in any of the Stations on the CBD and then get on the 781 bus to Mount Martha on bay 4 at Frankston Station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the great ocean road and the twelve apostles</title>
      <link>/post/the-great-ocean-road-and-the-twelve-apostles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-great-ocean-road-and-the-twelve-apostles/</guid>
      <description>First posted 4 years ago
We had a break from uni. It lasted one weekend, I believe it was Easter. What this means is that everyone wants to go away, travel to Tasmania, Southeast Asia, New Zealand, whichever. Things that I should have done but instead I wanted to enjoy the beauties the great State of Victoria could offer.
 Figure 1: Kensington Station  Friday I took the train to go see Emanuel and Nada at their home and we left for the camp in Elmore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>first impressions and the new friendship</title>
      <link>/post/first-impressions-and-the-new-friendship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/first-impressions-and-the-new-friendship/</guid>
      <description>First posted 4 years ago.
This is it, I thought as I was landing in Sydney. Suddenly my heart filled with emotion as I looked through the window and saw the Pacific Ocean for the first time. I had spent at least 30 hours inside a plane so I can’t tell if my eyes where watering because of sentiment or exhaustion but then again, it didn’t mattered. I had finally arrived.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>phillip island and the surfing attempt</title>
      <link>/post/phillip-island-and-the-surfing-attempt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/phillip-island-and-the-surfing-attempt/</guid>
      <description>First posted 4 years ago
It was a common Saturday morning. I woke up, had breakfast and got ready to go to church. We went to the Polish church in Dandenong where the wedding was held a week ago. So far so good. Nothing out of the ordinary had happened.
It happens that Emanuel has a childhood friend (if i can put it in those words) and he lives in Warragul.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>